Guide to the HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm, 1907-1993
HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm.
- Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Local Correspondence. 1981-1982.
  - Local 24., 1982; 39 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01239 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 25., 1981; 40 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01269 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 25., 1982; 41 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01278 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 26., 1981; 42 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01295 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 26., 1982; 43 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01316 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 27., 1981; 44 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01328 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 27., 1982; 45 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01363 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 28., 1981; 46 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01380 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 28., 1982; 47 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01463 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 29., 1981; 48 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01513 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 29., 1982; 49 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01551 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 30., 1981; 50 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01562 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 30., 1982; 51 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01587 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 30. Loan., 1982; 52 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01624 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 31., 1982; 53 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01657 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 32., 1981; 54 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01678 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 32., 1982; 55 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01684 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 34., 1982; 56 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01685 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 35., 1981; 57 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01694 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 35., 1982; 58 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01720 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 36., 1981; 59 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01731 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 36., 1982; 60 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01732 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 40., 1981; 61 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01768 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 40., 1982; 62 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01801 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 43., 1981; 63 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01831 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 43., 1982; 64 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01838 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 46., 1981; 65 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01849 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 46., 1982; 66 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01852 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 47., 1981; 67 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01871 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 47., 1982; 68 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01885 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 49., 1981; 69 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01891 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 49., 1982; 70 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01920 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 50., 1981; 71 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01949 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 50., 1982; 72 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01965 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 51., 1981; 73 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01990 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 51., 1982; 74 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01991 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 54., 1981; 75 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02026 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 54., 1982; 76 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02064 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 54. Loan., 1982; 77 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02126 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 165., 1982; 4 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00039 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 166., 1981; 5 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00064 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 166., 1982; 6 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00093 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 181., 1981; 7 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00124 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 181., 1982; 8 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00125 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 193., 1981; 9 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00129 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 193., 1982; 10 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00142 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 200., 1981; 11 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00145 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 200., 1982; 12 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00147 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 206., 1981; 13 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00162 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 206., 1982; 14 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00173 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 215., 1981; 15 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00184 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 215., 1982; 16 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00188 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 217., 1981; 17 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00193 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 217., 1982; 18 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00220 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 220., 1981; 19 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00234 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 220., 1982; 20 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00257 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 225., 1981; 21 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00272 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 225., 1982; 22 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00273 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 226., 1981; 23 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00276 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 226., 1982; 24 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00325 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 235., 1981; 25 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00355 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 235., 1982; 26 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00360 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 245., 1981; 27 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00373 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 245., 1982; 28 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00399 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 246., 1981; 29 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00400 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 246., 1982; 30 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00412 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 251., 1981; 31 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00413 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 251., 1982; 32 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00425 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 257., 1981; 33 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00428 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 257., 1982; 34 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00441 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 261., 1981; 35 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00445 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 261., 1982; 36 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00454 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 264., 1981; 37 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00467 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 264., 1982; 38 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00473 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 267., 1981; 39 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00484 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 267., 1982; 40 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00485 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 270., 1981; 41 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00489 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 270., 1982; 42 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00490 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 272., 1981; 43 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00497 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 272., 1982; 44 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00504 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 274., 1981; 45 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00510 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 274., 1982; 46 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00515 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 276., 1981; 47 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00532 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 276., 1982; 48 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00536 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 279., 1981; 49 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00543 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 279., 1982; 50 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00544 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 280., 1981; 51 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00550 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 280., 1982; 52 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00560 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 281., 1981; 53 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00568 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 281., 1982; 54 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00569 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 298., 1981; 55 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00572 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 298., 1982; 56 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00593 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 298. Loan., 1982; 57 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00635 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 301., 1981; 58 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00698 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 301., 1982; 59 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00707 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 309., 1981; 60 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00715 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 309., 1982; 61 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00739 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 310., 1981; 62 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00766 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 310. Loan., 1981; 63 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00767 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 310., 1982; 64 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00809 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 312., 1981; 65 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00810 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 312., 1982; 66 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00811 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 315., 1981; 67 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00819 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 315., 1982; 68 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00826 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 322., 1981; 69 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00828 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 322., 1982; 70 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00829 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 336., 1981; 71 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00846 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 336., 1982; 72 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00859 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 340., 1981; 73 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00860 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 340., 1982; 74 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00863 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 341., 1981; 75 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00878 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 341., 1982; 76 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00890 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 353., 1981; 77 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00891 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 353., 1982; 78 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00925 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 355., 1981; 79 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00935 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 355., 1982; 80 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00946 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 360., 1981; 81 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01026 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 360., 1982; 82 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01035 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 361., 1981; 83 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01049 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 361., 1982; 84 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01073 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 369., 1981; 85 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01077 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 369., 1982; 86 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01079 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 388., 1981; 87 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01082 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 388., 1982; 88 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01085 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 391., 1981; 89 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01112 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 391., 1982; 90 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01113 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 397., 1981; 91 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01120 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 397., 1982; 92 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01121 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 400., 1981; 93 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01124 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 400., 1982; 94 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01132 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 414., 1981; 95 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01135 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 414., 1982; 96 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01136 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 417., 1981; 97 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01140 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 417., 1982; 98 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01141 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 425., 1981; 99 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01144 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 425., 1982; 100 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01157 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 427., 1981; 101 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01172 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 427., 1982; 102 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01173 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 436., 1981; 103 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01192 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 436., 1982; 104 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01224 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 441., 1981; 105 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01254 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 441., 1982; 106 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01277 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 442., 1981; 107 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01282 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 442., 1982; 108 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01291 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 450., 1981; 109 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01295 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 450., 1982; 110 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01300 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 451., 1981; 111 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01310 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 451., 1982; 112 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01318 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 453., 1981; 113 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01330 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 453., 1982; 114 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01331 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 457., 1981; 115 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01348 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 457., 1982; 116 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01372 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 460., 1981; 117 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01410 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 460., 1982; 118 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01411 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 465., 1981; 119 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01414 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 465., 1982; 120 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01415 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 466., 1981; 121 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01423 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 466., 1982; 122 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01427 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 471., 1981; 123 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01438 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 471., 1982; 124 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01452 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 479., 1981; 125 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01472 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 479., 1982; 126 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01473 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 483., 1981; 127 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01476 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 483., 1982; 128 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01484 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 495., 1981; 129 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01508 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 495., 1982; 130 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01509 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 497., 1981; 131 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01512 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 497., 1982; 132 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01513 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 498., 1981; 133 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01518 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 498., 1982; 134 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01523 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 509., 1981; 135 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01537 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 509., 1982; 136 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01543 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 517., 1981; 137 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01550 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 517., 1982; 138 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01558 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 531., 1981; 139 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01564 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 531., 1982; 140 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01593 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 531. Loan., 1982; 141 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01615 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 533., 1981; 142 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01649 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 533., 1982; 143 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01690 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 535., 1981; 144 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01701 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 535. Loan., 1981; 145 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01737 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 535., 1982; 146 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01967 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 543., 1981; 147 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 01984 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 543., 1982; 148 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02004 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 550., 1981; 149 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02007 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 550., 1982; 150 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02014 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 555., 1981; 151 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02024 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 555., 1982; 152 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02059 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 569., 1981; 153 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02082 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 569., 1982; 154 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02088 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 570., 1981; 155 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02096 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 570., 1982; 156 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02097 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 588., 1981; 157 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02102 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 588., 1982; 158 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02103 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 604., 1981; 159 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02107 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 604., 1982; 160 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02118 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 610., 1981; 161 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02144 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 610., 1982; 162 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02145 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 623., 1981; 163 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02161 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 623., 1982; 164 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02162 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 628., 1981; 165 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02183 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 628., 1982; 166 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02189 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 631., 1981; 167 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02192 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 631., 1982; 168 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02208 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 634., 1981; 169 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02236 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 634., 1982; 170 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02244 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 636., 1981; 171 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02253 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 636., 1982; 172 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02254 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 646., 1981; 173 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02274 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 646., 1982; 174 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02275 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 657., 1981; 175 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02284 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 657., 1982; 176 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02285 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 662., 1981; 177 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02296 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 662., 1982; 178 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02297 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 681., 1981; 179 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02300 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 681., 1982; 180 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02308 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 688., 1981; 181 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02332 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 688., 1982; 182 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02333 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 703., 1981; 183 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02373 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 703., 1982; 184 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02374 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 737., 1981; 185 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02381 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 737., 1982; 186 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02398 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 741., 1981; 187 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02409 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 741., 1982; 188 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02410 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 746., 1981; 189 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02423 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 746., 1982; 190 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02426 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 767., 1981; 191 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02430 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 767., 1982; 192 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02456 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 772., 1981; 193 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02472 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 772., 1982; 194 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02475 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 775., 1981; 195 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02478 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 775., 1982; 196 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02479 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 779., 1981; 197 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02486 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 779., 1982; 198 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02499 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 791., 1981; 199 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02515 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 791., 1982; 200 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02516 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 803., 1981; 201 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02522 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 803., 1982; 202 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02523 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 804., 1981; 203 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02530 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 804., 1982; 204 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02531 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 806., 1981; 205 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02542 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 806., 1982; 206 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02548 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 810., 1981; 207 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02552 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 810., 1982; 208 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02553 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 814., 1981; 209 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02560 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 814., 1982; 210 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02569 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 828., 1981; 211 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02573 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 828., 1982; 212 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02579 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 836., 1981; 213 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02589 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 836., 1982; 214 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02593 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 838., 1981; 215 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02594 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 838., 1982; 216 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02600 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 847., 1981; 217 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02602 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 847., 1982; 218 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02624 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 860., 1981; 219 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02626 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 860., 1982; 220 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02645 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 863., 1981; 221 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02649 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 863., 1982; 222 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02660 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 867., 1981; 223 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02669 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 867., 1982; 224 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02674 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 868., 1981; 225 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02686 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 868., 1982; 226 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02699 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 873., 1981; 227 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02729 on Correspondence reel 2.